ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Union Depts., 1958-1965 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  Incl. memos to D.D. from officers of various depts. re their absence from office & their itineraries.
- Union Depts., 1951-1957 (Box 273, Folder 2a-2b)
- Union Depts. Asst. Exec. Secy. James Lipsig, 1955-1964 (Box 273, Folder 3a-3b)
- Union Depts. Auditing Dept., 1954-1965 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  Siemon L. Hamburger, Gen'l. Auditor.
- Union Depts. Circulation Dept., 1963-1966 (Box 273, Folder 5)
- Union Depts. Controller's Office, 1956-1962 (Box 273, Folder 6a)
- Union Depts. Education Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  Incl. report by Gus Tyler, 1962.
- Union Depts. Education Dept., 1951-1961 (Box 274, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. reports & memo's from Mark Starr (Director).
- Union Depts. Education Dept., 1940-1955 (Box 274, Folder 2a-2b)
- Union Depts. Education Dept., Officers' Institute, 1943-1959 (Box 274, Folder 3)
  Incl. syllabus for officers qualification course (N.D.).
- Union Depts. General Office, Office Staff, 1956-1962 (Box 274, Folder 4)
  Incl. letters of resignation from Hannah Haskel, April 1959, and Mark Starr, Aug. 1959.
- Union Depts. ILGWU Guide on Agreement. Provisions, Standards and Enforcement, 1965 (Box 274, Folder 5)
  (Union publ.)
- Union Depts. Housing, The Cooperative Houses, 1963-1964 (Box 274, Folder 6a-6b)
  Incl. letters requesting assistance in obtaining an apartment at the co-op houses.
- Union Depts. Housing, The Cooperative Houses, 1962 (Box 275, Folder 1a-1b)
- Union Depts. Housing, Cooperative Houses, 1960-1961 (Box 275, Folder 2a-2b)
- Union Depts. Housing, Cooperative Houses, 1956-1959 (Box 275, Folder 3a-3b)
- Union Depts. Housing Cooperative Housing, Dedication Ceremonies, May 19, 1962. (Box 275, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. congratulatory messages; invitations to attend ceremony; D.D. speech at dedication.
- Union Depts. Housing, East River Housing, Inc. (Box 275, Folder 5a-5b)
- Union Depts. Housing, East River Housing, Inc., 1950-1966 (Box 276, Folder 1a-1b)
  I.c.w. Abraham Kazan (President), East River Housing Corp., & Elias Lieberman re project; requests for apartments; plans for development.
- Union Depts. Housing, East River Housing, Inc., Dedication Ceremony, 1955 (Box 276, Folder 2a-2b)
  Oct. 22, 1955. Incl. lists of participants, congratulatory messages, literature on International Cooperative Village, (some misfiling in folder)
- Union Depts. Housing, Penn Station South, 1959-1962 (Box 276, Folder 3)
- Union Depts. International Labor Relations Dept., 1939-1964 (Box 276, Folder 4a-4c)
  Corres. w. Jay Lovestone (Director); incl. correspondence. when he was Director of Dept. of Int'l. Affairs, AFL-CIO; Secretary, Free Trade Union Comm.; on editorial board, Workers Acre? reports.
- Union Depts. Investigations, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  Records on investigation in Local 102.
- Union Depts. Investment Dept., 1955-1965 (Box 277, Folder 2a-2b)
  Letters & reports from Charles Brush (Director); requests for Union participation in projects.
- Union Depts. Justice, 1940-1966 (Box 277, Folder 3a-3b)
- Union Depts. Lespier, Tony (Editor), Justicia., 1963-1965 (Box 277, Folder 4)
- Union Depts. Legal Dept., 1941-1965 (Box 277, Folder 5a-5d)
  Corres. w. Morris P. Glushien (General Counsel) & James Lipsig.
- Union Depts. Management-Engineering, 1950-1964 (Box 278, Folder 1a-1b)
  Sept. 1950-64. Corres., reports.
- Union Depts. Master Agreements Dept., 1965-1966 (Box 278, Folder 1c)
  Letters & reports from Wilbur Daniels (Director).
- Union Depts. Officers, Charged, Suspended or Expelled, 1939-1965 (Box 278, Folder 2a-2c)
  Arranged alphabetically by officer.
- Union Depts. Organizing Campaign, 1955 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  Corres. & literature on one-dollar-per-hour minimum wage drive.
- Union Depts. Photography Dept., 1950-1955 (Box 278, Folder 4)
- Union Depts. Political Dept., 1948-1966 (Box 278, Folder 5a-5b)
- Union Depts. Letters and reports from Evelyn Dubrow (Legislative Representative), Gus Tyler (Director). (Box 279, Folder 1a-1b)
  Submitted contributions to Finance Dept.; analysis of 1964 presidential campaign & NYC election.
- Union Depts. Promotions Dept., 1950-1960 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  Harry Crone (Promotions Director).
- Union Depts. Requested Wage Increases From Officers, 1955-1960 (Box 279, Folder 3a-3b)
  July 1955-60. Incl. officers' salary schedule.
- Union Depts. Requested Wage Increases, 1943-1954 (Box 279, Folder 4a-4b)
- Union Depts. Research Dept., Lazare Teper (Director), 1953-1966 (Box 280, Folder 1a-1c)
  Incl. statistical reports in the garment industry; minimum wages; Consumer Price Index; legislation to the Fair Labor Standards Act; statements of Lazare Teper before committees & related correspondence.
- Union Depts. Scholarships, 1956-1964 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  Congratulatory messages from D.D. to winners of International Scholarship Fund Award & acknowledgments from recipients.
- Union Depts. Stulberg, Louis (General Secretary-Treasurer), 1959-1965 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  Biographical data.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 280, Folder 4a-4d)
  Corres. re Union Label campaigns, especially Judy Bond campaign; adver­tising, film promotions, leaflets; I.c.w. Eleanor Lambert, retained by Union to direct promotion programs 1959-63; report, "Attitudes of American Women Toward Trade Unions in America, 1962."
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1961 (Box 281, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. newspaper advertising.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1960 (Box 281, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. Nat'l. Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Bd. on Union labels.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1958-1959 (Box 281, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. acknowledgments for D.D. sending inscribed thimble, commemorating the inauguration of the ILGWU label, 1959.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1936-1956 (Box 281, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. newspaper clippings, ads in Women's Wear Daily, 1936-37.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., Matheson, Min L. (Director), 1946-1964 (Box 281, Folder 5)
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1959-1960 (Box 282, Folder 1a-1c)
  Corres. w. label advertising agency, Doyle, Dane, Bernbach, Inc.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., 1962-1966 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. label advertising agency, Wexton Company, Inc.
- Union Depts. Union Label Dept., Canadian Union Label, 1961-1963 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  July 1961-Jan. 1963. I.c.w. Bernard Shane.
- Social Insurance Programs. Death Benefit Dept., 1956-1966 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Harry Haskel (Director). Haskel statement to Sub- Committee on Anti-Trust & Monopoly of Senate Comm. on Judiciary, July 1964.
- S.I.P. Death Benefit Dept., 1939-1955 (Box 282, Folder 5a-5d)
  Goodman Block (Director) 1945-55. Corres. re Death Benefit claims.
- S.I.P. Death Benefit Fund for Children of Union Officers, 1954-1958 (Box 283, Folder 1)
- S.I.P. Death Benefit Dept., 1963-1966 (Box 283, Folder 2a-2b)
  Referrals to D.B. or Health & Welfare Dept.
- S.I.P. Health, Welfare and Vacation Dept. (H & W), 1962-1965 (Box 283, Folder 3)
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., 1942-1961 (Box 283, Folder 4a-4d)
  Incl. letters from Adolph Held (Director) re Dept. rules & regulations, loans made to Dept., collections received for Fund; separate fund for vacation fund.
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., Boston, 1956-1957 (Box 283, Folder 5)
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., Canada, 1944-1955 (Box 283, Folder 6)
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., Eastern Region Cloak & Dress, 1943-1949 (Box 283, Folder 7)
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., Mid-West Region, 1950-1957 (Box 283, Folder 8)
- S.I.P. H and W Dept., Minutes. H & W Funds Committee of the GEB, 1952-1957 (Box 283, Folder 9)
  prior to 1952, minutes of the H & W & D.B. Comm., 1949-51.
- S.I.P. H and W, New York, 1944-1963 (Box 284, Folder 1a-1b)
- S.I.P. H and W, Northeast Dept., 1949-1955 (Box 284, Folder 2)
- S.I.P. H and W, Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1946-1963 (Box 284, Folder 3a-3b)
- S.I.P. H and W, Pacific Coast Region, 1954-1958 (Box 284, Folder 4)
- S.I.P. H and W, Philadelphia Region, 1944-1961 (Box 284, Folder 5)
- S.I.P. H and W, Puerto Rico, 1956-1963 (Box 284, Folder 6a-6b)
  I.c.w. Robert Gladnick (Manager), Local 600 re Mobile Health Unit for P.R.
- S.I.P. H and W, Southeastern Region, 1954-1957 (Box 284, Folder 7)
- S.I.P. H and W, Southwestern Region, 1946-1958 (Box 284, Folder 8)
- S.I.P. H and W, So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1946-1961 (Box 284, Folder 9)
- S.I.P. H and W, Special Fund. Incl. rules of special fund & schedule of collections, 1955-1965 (Box 284, Folder 10)
- S.I.P. H and W, Upper South Dept., 1947-1957 (Box 284, Folder 11)
- S.I.P. Retirement Funds (R.F.), Boston, 1952-1957 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  Corres. re cases.
- S.I.P. R.F., Canada., 1951-1963 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Bernard Shane, David Randolph (Administrator), Montreal Dress Industry Health Fund re cases.
- S.I.P. R.F., Cleveland, 1949-1959 (Box 285, Folder 3a-3b)
- S.I.P. R.F., Eastern Region, 1962-1965 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  Incl. minutes of Bd. of Trustees, Eastern Region R.F.
- S.I.P. R.F., Eastern Region, 1951-1959 (Box 285, Folder 5a-5e)
  Incl. rules & regulations, financial reports, correspondence. w. Adolph Held (Administrator). (Incl. E.O.T., N.E., C.O.T.)
- S.I.P. R.F., Employment for Retirees, 1958 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  May 1958. Incl. survey of community centers for Union retirees in NYC, prepared by Abe Bluestein.
- S.I.P. R.F., Increases in Benefits, 1966 (Box 286, Folder 1a-1d)
  Thank-you letters.
- S.I.P. R.F., Mid-West Region, 1953-1964 (Box 286, Folder 2)
- S.I.P. R.F., N.Y. Coat and Suit Industry, 1954-1965 (Box 286, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. meeting of Bd. of Trustees of Coat & Suit Industry; correspondence. w. Union members.
- S.I.P. R.F., N.Y. Coat and Suit Industry, 1943-1953 (Box 286, Folder 4a-4b)
- Incl. rules and regulations; Investigating Committee report on financial practices of Fund, 1952 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  Aug. 1952, correspondence. re cases.
- S.I.P. R.F., N.Y. Dress Industry., 1947-1965 (Box 287, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. rules & regulations of the Retirement Fund; 1947; correspondence. re cases.
- S.I.P. R.F., N.Y. Locals. (Box 287, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. correspondence. re cases arranged numerically by local.
- S.I.P. R.F., Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1949-1963 (Box 287, Folder 4)
- S.I.P. R.F., Pacific Coast Region, 1955-1960 (Box 287, Folder 5)
- S.I.P. R.F., Philadelphia Region, 1958-1964 (Box 287, Folder 6)
- S.I.P. R.F., So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1952-1955 (Box 287, Folder 7)
- S.I.P. R.F., Southwest Region. (Box 287, Folder 8)
- S.I.P. R.F., Retirement Reciprocity. (Box 287, Folder 9a-9b)
  Corres. w. officers of Fund.
- S.I.P. R.F., Staff Retirement Fund, 1962-1966 (Box 288, Folder 1a-1c)
  Letters from Louis Rolnick on staff applying for retirement; report, 1965.
- S.I.P. R.F., Staff Retirement Fund, 1948-1961 (Box 288, Folder 2a-2e)
  Corres. w. Adolph Held; minutes of meeting of Staff Retirement Fund, Aug. 22, 1952, 1948, also correspondence. on format1on of Staff Retirement Fund.
- S.I.P. R.F., Staff Retirement, 1962-1966 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  Corres. w. retired officers.
- S.I.P. R.F., Supplementary Unemployment Severance Benefits Fund, 1963-1965 (Box 288, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. reports, rules & regulations & by-laws of the Fund.
- S.I.P. R.F., Supplementary Unemployment Severance Benefits Fund, 1958-1962 (Box 288, Folder 5)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Allentown District Council, 1952-1959 (Box 290, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Baltimore Jt. Bd., 1952-1959 (Box 290, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Boston Jt. Bd., 1952-1961 (Box 290, Folder 3a-3c)
  Corres. w. Philip Kramer.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Chicago Jt. Bd., 1962-1966 (Box 290, Folder 4a-4b)
  I.c.w. Morris Bialis on reorganization of Rothmoor Garment Co., retirement of Union members, 1963-66.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Chicago Jt. Bd., 1952-1961 (Box 290, Folder 5a-5b)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Cincinnati Jt. Bd., 1952-1958 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  I.c.w. David Solomon, Nicholas Kirtzman.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Cleveland Jt. Bd., 1952-1959 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  Corres. w. N. Kirtzman.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Cleveland Knit goods Council, 1958-1960 (Box 291, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Dallas Jt. Bd., 1951-1955 (Box 291, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Kansas City Joint Board., 1952-1964 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. Helen Bengtson.
- Jt. Bd. and D.C.: Kansas City Jt. Bd., 1948-1956 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. Meyer Perlstein on organizing campaign; copies of letters sent to James Reed, representative of firm; printed material.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Los Angeles Cloak Jt. Bd., 1962-1966 (Box 291, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. Isidor Stenzor on Retirement Fund of Bd; bargaining agreements w. L. A. Coat & Suit Mfrs. Assoc.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1959-1962 (Box 291, Folder 6a-6d)
  Corres. w. Stenzor re Communist activities in Jt. Bd., 1962 election & resolution on Communist candidates; 1959 election; testimony of Ben Margolis before the Joint fact-finding Committee on Un-American Activities, Jan. 1946.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Jt. Bd., 1942-1958 (Box 292, Folder 1a-1c)
  I.c.w. J. Mencoff, 1942-56; correspondence. w. Samuel Otto & Stenzor on whether managers are to be included w. election of other officers; complaints; contract agreements; charges brought by affiliated locals of Jt. Bd. against I. Stenzor, 1955-56.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1950-1955 (Box 292, Folder 2a-2c)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Cloak Jt. Bd. Building, 1954-1958 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  Finances of Jt. Bd. bldg.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Dress & Sportswear Jt. Bd., 1963-1965 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. John Ulene.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Dress & Sportswear Jt. Bd., 1950-1955 (Box 292, Folder 5a-5b)
  Incl. proposed rules & regulations of L. A. Dress & Sportswear, Retirement Fund; correspondence. w. Fannie Borax re merger of the L. A. Dress Jt. Bd. & the L. A. Sportswear Jt. Council, Sept. 7, 1955.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: L. A. Jt. Council, 1950-1951 (Box 293, Folder 1a-1b)
  I.c.w. Hyman D. Langer & William Ross.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Miami Jt. Council, 1962-1964 (Box 293, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. Robert Gladnick (Manager), Local 415, on firms, Hialeah Dress Co. & Bobbie Brooks.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Miami Jt. Council, 1956-1961 (Box 293, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. agreement between Union & Wellesley, Inc., 1960; correspondence. w. Max Wexler (State Director of Union) on organizing activities; census, 1958.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Miami Jt. Council, 1954-1955 (Box 293, Folder 4a-4d)
  Corres. w. Abraham Plotkin, Samuel Macy & Robert Gladnick on organizing & contract agreement w. firms; internal Union problems.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Miami Jt. Council, 1951-1953 (Box 294, Folder 1a-1d)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Milwaukee Jt. Bd., 1958-1959 (Box 294, Folder 2)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Montreal Cloak Jt. Council & Dress Jt. Bd., 1962-1964 (Box 294, Folder 3a-3e)
  Letters from Bernard Shane on organizing activities; jurisdictional dispute bet. Union & Amalgamated Clothing Workers Union; agreement w. Montreal Cloak Mfrs. Assoc.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Montreal Cloak Jt. Council & Dress Jt. Bd., 1956-1961 (Box 295, Folder 1a-1c)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Montreal Cloak Jt. Council & Dress Jt. Bd., 1951-1955 (Box 295, Folder 2a-2d)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Montreal Cloak Jt. Council & Dress Jt. Bd., 1953-1959 (Box 295, Folder 3a-3b)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Montreal Cloak Jt. Council & Dress Jt. Bd., 1964-1966 (Box 295, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. w. Bernard Shane.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1962-1965 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Henoch Mendelsund; report.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1951-1961 (Box 296, Folder 2a-2d)
  I.c.w. Isidore Nagler; report, 1953.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1962-1965 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  Corres. w. Charles Zimmerman.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Cloak Jt. Bd., 1951-1961 (Box 296, Folder 4a-4b)
  Julius Hochman letter of resignation, June 1958; correspondence. on charges brought by Hochman against Min Lurye Matheson, 1952.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., Disability & Health Plans Dept., 1958-1960 (Box 296, Folder 5)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., Health Plan, 1955-1957 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  Letters from Jack Spitzer; health plans for Union.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress Institute, 1940-1956 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  Incl. Jt. Bd. releases on agreement w. Dress employers, 1941.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., Ladies Apparel Accessories Council, 1940-1950 (Box 297, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., Lurye, William, Union Organizer., 1949-1954 (Box 297, Folder 2a-2b)
  Corres. w. Min (Lurye) Matheson (sister of William), members of family, officers & N.Y. officials re case of Benedicto Marci, accused in killing of Wm. Lurye, May 9, 1949; literature; Dress Jt. Bd. releases; & newspaper clippings.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd. Negotiations, 1964 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  Corres. on impending strike & settlement, Feb. 1964.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress Strike, 1958 (Box 297, Folder 4a-4e)
  Corres. w. Union officers, releases, broadsides, newspaper clippings, D.D. notes on strike.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress Strike, 1958 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  Strike memoranda.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress Strike, 1958 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  Telegrams; support of strike and congratulatory messages upon bringing strike to successful conclusion.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dress Jt. Bd., N.Y. Dress Strike Disturbances, 1958 (Box 297, Folder 7)
  I.e. & printed material on strike in Pennsylvania.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dressmakers Jt. Council, 1962-1964 (Box 298, Folder 1)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: N.Y. Dressmakers Jt. Council, 1959-1961 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  Statement of receipts & disbursements for General Strike of 1958.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Pacific Coast Office, 1962-1964 (Box 298, Folder 3a-3b)
  Corres. w. Samuel Otto, on organizing campaigns & agreement w. firms.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Pacific Coast Office, 1951-1961 (Box 298, Folder 4a-4e)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Philadelphia Cloak Joint Board., 1952-1960 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Harry Dordick.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Philadelphia Dress Jt. Bd., 1962-1966 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. William Ross; collective agreement w. Philadelphia Apparel Producers Assoc. 1962.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Philadelphia Dress Jt. Bd., 1950-1961 (Box 299, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. agreement bet. Union & Phila. Coat & Suit Assoc., 1961
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Philadelphia Dress Jt. Bd., 1952-1954 (Box 299, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. re Josephine Spica & Al Gerber cases (Business Agents), 1952-54.
- Jt. Bd. and D.C.: Phila. Jt. Council, 1952-1966 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Louis Bulkin.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Phila. & So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1962-1965 (Box 299, Folder 6)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Phila. & So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1940-1960 (Box 299, Folder 7a-7b)
  I.c.w. Barnett Karp re merger of the Phila. Cloakmakers Union & the So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1955
- Joint Board. and D.C.: San Antonio Jt. Bd., 1951-1960 (Box 299, Folder 8)
  I.c.w. Frederick Siems re strike activities at Tex-Son, correspondence. on Texas firms.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: San Francisco Jt. Bd., 1962-1965 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Cornelius Wall & Jennie Matyas.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: San Francisco Jt. Bd., 1951-1961 (Box 300, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Wall & Otto re Lawrence Mirgon case. President, Local 213, 1961.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Scranton District Council, 1954-1959 (Box 300, Folder 3)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Seattle Jt. Bd., 1951-1958 (Box 300, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Eloise Pratt.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: So. Jersey Jt. Bd., 1952-1963 (Box 300, Folder 5)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: St. Louis Cloak & Dress Jt. Bd. Cotton Dress & Allied Industries, 1962 (Box 300, Folder 6)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: St. Louis Cloak & Dress Jt. Bd. Cotton Dress & Allied Industries, 1951-1960 (Box 300, Folder 7)
- Joint Board. and B.C.: St. Louis Jt. Bd., Forest City Mfg. Co., 1940-1959 (Box 300, Folder 8a-8b)
  I.c.w. Frederick Sieras, Meyer Perlstein on agreement w. co., incl. collective agreement.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Toronto Jt. Bd., 1951-1964 (Box 300, Folder 9a-9b)
  I.c.w. S. Kraisman; report by Jim Kitts (Director); Toronto Organizing, Dec. 1966.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Twin Cities Jt. Bd., 1962 (Box 300, Folder 10)
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Twin Cities Jt. Bd., 1951-1960 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  I.c.w. Michael Finkelstein.
- Joint Board. and D.C.: Winnipeg Cloak Jt. Bd., 1951-1961 (Box 300, Folder 12a-12b)
  I.c.w. Bernard Shane on Union agreement w. Winnipeg Ladies' Cloak & Suit Mfrs. Assoc.; correspondence. w. Sam Herbst.
- K (Box 301, Folder 1)
  Kennedy Bust. Form letters for distribution.
- Kennedy Bust, Distribution. (Box 301, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. Union officers on persons to receive bust.
- Labor Day, 1959-1961 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  Corres. re Labor Day Parades.
- Kennedy Bust, Distribution. (Box 301, Folder 3a-3e)
  Acknowledgments on receiving bust.
- L, 1962-1966 (Box 302, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. eulogy of Frank Liberti by Gus Tyler, 1966.
- L, 1952-1951 (Box 302, Folder 2a-2d)
  Incl. correspondence. on the Longview Foundation Project co-sponsored by Union; exhibition of paintings at Whitney Museum, 1959.
- LaGuardia, Fiorello H., 1954-1959 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  Corres. re LaGuardia Memorial.
- Legislation. A., 1941-1947 (Box 302, Folder 5a-5b)
  Incl. correspondence. on Anti-Poll Tax Bill; letters from Grover A. Whalen & copies of correspondence. bet. LaGuardia & Whalen on bill to establish Apparel Industry Development Corporation, 1941.
- Legislation. B-C. (Box 302, Folder 6a-6b)
- Legislation. Consumer, 1962 (Box 303, Folder 1)
- Legislation. D-E, 1940-1957 (Box 303, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. correspondence. on displaced persons, 1947-50? Equal Rights Amendment, 1940- 57.
- Legislation. F-G. (Box 303, Folder 3)
- Legislation. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1955-1958 (Box 303, Folder 4a-4d)
  July 1955-58. Incl. correspondence. on Puerto Rico Minimum wage amendments.
- Legislation. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1955 (Box 303, Folder 5a-5b)
  April-June 1955. Incl. D.D. statement before the Labor Subcommittee of the Senate Committee on Labor & Public Welfare, April.
- Legislation. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1955 (Box 304, Folder 1)
- Legislation. Fair Labor Standards Act, 1955 (Box 304, Folder 2a-2b)
  Jan-Mar. 1955. Corres. w. U.S. Senators on need for revision of F.L.S. in Puerto Rico & Virgin Islands.
- Legislation. Foreign Trade, 1962 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  Incl. joint statement by Lazare Teper & Hilton Fried (Director of Research), Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America on problems in textile industry before Committee on Inter-State & Foreign Trade.
- Legislation. H-I, 1937-1959 (Box 304, Folder 4a-4c)
  Incl. bill on Housing, 1937-59? Immigration. 1952.
- Legislation. Health Medical Care for the Aged, 1962 (Box 304, Folder 5)
- Legislation. J-L. (Box 304, Folder 6a-6c)
- Legislation. Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1959-1961 (Box 305, Folder 1a-1c)
  The Landrum-Griffin Act, Kennedy-Ervin Bill.
- Legislation. M-N. (Box 305, Folder 2a-2b)
- Legislation. Minimum Wage Union Campaign, 1955-1961 (Box 305, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. D.D. statement before Sub­committee on Labor Standards of the House Committee on Labor, April 1960; Lazare Teper statement before Subcommittee on Labor, Senate Committee on Labor & Public Welfare, May 1959; correspondence. w. John F. Kennedy, Wayne Morse & Arthur J. Goldberg on Kennedy-Morse-Roosevelt Minimum Wage bills, 1959.
- Legislation. O-R. (Box 306, Folder 1a-1b)
- Legislation. S-T. (Box 306, Folder 2a-2b)
- Legislation. St. Lawrence Seaway Project, 1950-1957 (Box 306, Folder 3)